Guess who just made number two?
Jackass Number Two is a action, comedy,
documentary film directed by Jeff Tremaine.
Jackass Number Two is a compilation of various stunts,
pranks and skits, and essentially has no plot.
Chris Pontius, Johnny Knoxville, Steve-O, Bam Margera, and the whole crew
return to the screen to raise the stakes higher than ever before.
Self, played by Johnny Knoxville.
Self, played by Bam Margera.
Self, played by Steve-O.
Self, played by Chris Pontius.
Self, played by Ryan Dunn.
Self, played by Jason 'Wee Man' Acuña.
Jackass Number Two is a 2006 American reality slapstick comedy film directed by Jeff
Tremaine, and produced by Tremaine, Spike Jonze, and Johnny Knoxville.
It is the sequel to Jackass: The Movie (2002), both
based upon the MTV series Jackass.
Like its predecessor and the original television show, the film is a compilation of stunts, pranks and skits, starring the regular Jackass cast
of Johnny Knoxville, Bam Margera, Dave England, Ryan Dunn, Chris Pontius, Wee Man, Steve-O, Preston Lacy, and Ehren McGhehey.
Produced by MTV Films, Dickhouse Productions and Lynch Siderow Productions, and distributed by Paramount Pictures, the film premiered in theaters on September
22, 2006, received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed $84.6 million worldwide against a production budget of $11.5 million.
Unused material of the film was released as a separate movie titled Jackass 2.5
online on December 19, 2007, and on DVD on December 26, 2007.
It was followed by another sequel, Jackass 3D (2010).
The film explores themes of pain, wound, disgust, stunt, stuntman.
The tone is lighthearted.